<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Aspigirlcodes | Blog</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <updated>2018-07-24T12:21:29+02:00</updated>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <uri></uri>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Ear Protectors&#58; an overview</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/ear-protectors"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/ear-protectors</id>
   <updated>2018-07-05T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Being sensitive to sound can make peoples’ day to day lifes exhausting, and even may exclude them from taking part in certain activities. Before I was diagnosed autistic I didn’t even realise that I was more sensitive to sound than most people. There is this idea we all have, that...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>One and a half month into a new hobby&#58; 10 sketchnotes</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/sketchnotes"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/sketchnotes</id>
   <updated>2018-07-02T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It was an overwhelming start, almost 2 months ago. The workshop took place in a room I don’t know, with half of the people I had never seen before. It lasted a whole afternoon and included a fair bit of talking (which I mainly skipped). It was so hard I...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Summer Books Review</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/summer-books-review"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/summer-books-review</id>
   <updated>2017-10-02T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This summer I ordered three autism related books. Although they were very different, I enjoyed reading all three of them very much. The books are:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The State of Grace by Rachael Lucas,&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Odd Girl Out by Laura James, and&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Autism and Asperger Syndrome in Adults by Luke Beardon.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Nachteilsausgleich, mehr als nur ein schönes Wort?</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/nachteilsausgleich"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/nachteilsausgleich</id>
   <updated>2017-09-13T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jetzt, wo ich drauf und dran bin, mein zweites Bachelorstudium abzuschliessen und zuvor bereits an 2 Unis war, möchte ich gern etwas über Nachteilsausgleich schreiben. Oder genauer gesagt über &lt;strong&gt;Nachteilsausgleich für Autisten an Universitäten und anderen Hochschulen&lt;/strong&gt;. Ziel ist, dass die darin enthaltenen Informationen anderen helfen. Wenn alles klappt, möchte...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Nice design, but utterly confusing (accessibility)</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/confusing-design"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/confusing-design</id>
   <updated>2017-08-13T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jesslynnrose/status/896297773066317824&quot;&gt;this survey screenshot on twitter&lt;/a&gt;. It is the perfect example of how something that most people find nice and funny, can be utterly confusing to me. To be honest, I would probably abandon the survey right at this screen. Not because I don’t want to be nice...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>The art of interacting with an autistic software developer (Talk transcript)</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/autistic-software-developer-talk"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/autistic-software-developer-talk</id>
   <updated>2017-07-26T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is the Transcript of my talk given at Djangocon Europe in 2017. You can find &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/oTuhqnWRt84&quot;&gt;the youtube video here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://speakerdeck.com/githubsara/the-art-of-interacting-with-an-autistic-software-developer&quot;&gt;slides can be found here&lt;/a&gt;. I want to thank the Djangocon community for giving me the opportunity and being supportive, My company, 89Grad, for giving me the time...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Weighted Blanket DIY</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/weighted-blanket"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/weighted-blanket</id>
   <updated>2017-06-14T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/gewichtsdecke&quot;&gt;Diese Anleitung gibt es auch auf Deutsch.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Since my diagnosis I know now for sure that fighting overloads doesn’t work. So I often end up hiding under a blanket on the couch or in my bed. Sometimes I listen to music, sometimes even that is too much. It is...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Gewichtsdecke (Anleitung)</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/gewichtsdecke"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/gewichtsdecke</id>
   <updated>2017-05-20T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/weighted-blanket&quot;&gt;This post also exists in English.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Seit ich weiss, dass es nichts bringt Overloads zu bekämpfen, verschanze ich mich oft unter eine Decke im Schlafzimmer oder auf dem Sofa. Manchmal höre ich dann Musik. Manchmal ist auch das mir zu viel. In diesen Phasen, wo ich das Pulsieren und...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>The more accessible way to ask for a phone number</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/accessible-phone"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/accessible-phone</id>
   <updated>2017-05-19T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This project consists of a small demo showing the problems and suggesting some solutions. I talked about this in my very first lighting talk ever at Djangocon Europe 2017.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can view the &lt;a href=&quot;https://aspigirlcodes.github.io/accessiblephone/&quot;&gt;demo here&lt;/a&gt;, and find the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/aspigirlcodes/accessiblephone&quot;&gt;source code here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;introduction&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Over the years phones have...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>10 Prejudices that lead me to believe I couldn't possibly be autistic</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/10-prejudices-autism"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/10-prejudices-autism</id>
   <updated>2017-04-30T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I was diagnosed with autism in my late twenties. But that doesn’t mean I didn’t think about the possibility that I could be autistic long before that. While seeing my younger brother and cousins (all boys) getting diagnosed, being a trained inclusion responsible for autistic kids on summer camps and...</content>
 </entry>

 

</feed>